A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject files of the Director of the Department of Historic Resources, 1966-2007
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and Subject Files, 1966-2007.
  - 1984-2007 (Accession 45554)., 27 cu. ft. (27 box).
    - Kennons in Amelia Wildlife Refuge, 1997. (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Kernstown Battlefield, 1996-2005. (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Kiskaik - Yorktown Naval Weapons Station, 2004. (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Kroger Limited Partnership v. Department of Historic Resources, 2004. (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Land Conservation Foundation, 2000. (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Land Issue - State Holdings and Easements, 1995. (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Archaeological Study of Colonial Chesapeake Bay Culture, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Archaeology Week: Virginia, 1996. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Architectural Evaluation Committee, 1996. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Architectural Literacy - Calder Loth Course at Virginia Military Institute, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Architectural Survey Forms, 1995. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Archives Scanning Project, 1996. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Arlington County/ Constituent Letter/ Maywood Neighborhood, 1994-1996. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Articles, 1996-2000. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Artifact Loans - Virginia Historical Society, 2000. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Asburn Historic District: Loudoun County, Va., 2002. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - ASV, 1994-1999. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Art and Architectural Review Board, 1996-1997. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Assembly Contact - Buck Slips, 1997. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Assembly Information Requests, 1994-1996. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Attorney General Correspondence, 1989-2001. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Barboursville - General Shale, 2002-2003. (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Barn Again, 2002-2004. (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Becky Norton Dunlop - Secretary of Natural Resources, 1995-1996. (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Best Roles for Regional Office and Department of Historic Resources Central Office, 1995-1997. (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Biennial Issues Assessment Report, 1998-2000. (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Blair Middle School: Norfolk, Va., 2002. (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Bloomsbury: Orange County, Va., unknown. (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Board of Historic Resources, 2001-2002. (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Board Meetings, 1996-1999. (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Bocock Streetcar - Science Museum of Virginia, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Brandy Station Battlefield - Bristoe Station Battlefield, 1989-1995. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Bristoe Station, 1990-1998. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - John Broadwater, 1996-1997. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Brook Run, 2004. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Brookneal, 2004. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Brownfields Redevelopment and ACG Conference, 1998-1999. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - lyle Browning Correspondence, 1992-2005. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Lyle Browning, 2001-2002. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Budget, 1999-2000. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Budget, 1994-1995. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Budget, 1996-1997. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Budget, 1996-2002. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Budget, 1998. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Northampton County Survey, 1995. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Notes/Letters of Thanks, 1995-1996. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Northern Virginia Association for History, Inc.: Northumberland, Va., 1998. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - National Parks Service Grant, 1998. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - National Trust for Historic Places's Preservation Leadership Training Initiative, 1996. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Notes on Virginia, 1998-1999. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Nottoway River Survey, 2003. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Oak Hill/ John Marshall, 1993-1994. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Oakwood Cemetery, 1995-2002. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Obia Memorial Hospital, 2003. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Occoneechee State Park, 2004. (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Olympic Committee, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Operation Spruce-Up, 1997. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Oregon Hill District, 1996-1997. (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Oregon Hill/ Ethyl Corporation, 1996-1997. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Oregon Hill Home Improvement Council (OHHIC), 2004. (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Partnership for Achieving Successful Schools (PASS) Initiative, 2002. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Preservation Alliance of Virginia Conference, 2003. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Preservation Alliance of Virginia Conference, 2002. (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Preservation Alliance of Virginia Cooperative Issues, 2001-2004. (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Preservation Alliance of Virginia Newsletters, 2002-2003. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Preservation Alliance of Virginia Preservation Award, 2001-2002. (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Preservation Alliance of Virginia, 1994-2001. (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Museums on the Boulevard, 1997-2004. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Museums on the Boulevard, 1997-2000. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Myer, Walter K., 1996. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA), 1997-2004. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - North American Graves Protection and Repatriation Act (NAGPRA) and National Museum of Natural History (NMNH)- In a Nutshell, unknown. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - NASA Visit, 2006. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - National Bulletin - To National Parks Service, 1996. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - National Center for Preservation Technology, 1995. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Nanzatico, 1995-2003. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - National Historic Preservation Act - Hearing on committee Resources, 2005. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - National Park and Public Lands, 1997. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Abingdon Visit, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Accomplishments, 1995-2004. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Alliance to Conserve Old Richmond Neighborhoods (ACORN), 2004-2005. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Administration (Hiring Requests, Procurement, etc.), 1996-2005. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Advisory Council on Historic Preservation, 1995-1997. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, 1997. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Advisory Council/ Affordable Housing, 1997-1998. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - African American Cultural Tourism, 2000. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Agency Heads Meeting, 2003. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Agency Land Conservation Coordinating Meeting, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Agency Treasury Loan, 1996. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - American Institute of Architects: Northern Virginia, 2004. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Alex Wise - Former Director Correspondence, 1994-2000. (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - American Heritage Rivers Initiative, 1997. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Antenna Audio, 2000. (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Archaeology, 1990-2003. (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Archaeology Board, 2001. (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Archaeology Commission, 1999-2000. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Archaeology Museums, 1994. (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Archaeology - Fox Site, 1994. (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Budget, 1999. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Budget, 2003. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 2004. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Budget/ Session, 2005. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Budget, 2005. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Building the Case for Preservation - Va. Enforcement Assessment, 1997. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Burial Task Force Meeting, 2003-2004. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Burns and McDonnell Fiber Optic Cable, 1997. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Bypass 29/ Schlessinger Farm, 1996. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Business Registration Guide (State Corporation Commission), 2005. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Calder Loth Speeches, 1995. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Callander Farm, 2004. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Camp Winonah: Appomattox County, Va., 2004. (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Capital Region office Responses, 1996-1997. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Capital Region Preservation Office - Opening Ceremony, 1996. (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Cemeteries Survey, 1996-1998. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Center for Private Conservation, 1998. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - central Virginia Battlefield Trust, 2005. (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Certificate of Recognition - Governor George Allen for Department of Historic Resources/ Chippokes Plantation State Park, unknown. (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - House and Senate Documents, 1992-1999. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - House of Delegates Retreat - Douthat, 1994. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - House of Representatives, 1995-2000. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Housing Conference, 1995. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Housing Opportunities Made Equal, 2006. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Howard MacCord, 1987-2004. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Human resources, 1994-1999. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Hunt, Conover - Resume, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Hurricane Katrina, 2005. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Hylton, Tom, 1996-1997. (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Information Management and Information Security, 1994-1999. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Interagency Code Commission, 1994. (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - House and Senate Documents, 1992-1999. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Integrated Preservation Software, 1996-1997. (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Interstate Rest Stops/ Rest Areas, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Information Technology, 2000. (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Infantry Flag 28th Virginia, 1998-2000. (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Invitations, 2002-2005. (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Gaston (Hurricane/Tropical Storm), 2004. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - General Assembly Grants, 2000. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - General Assembly 2003, 2003. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Grant Fund, 1999-2001. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - General Robert E. Lee, 1996-2004. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - George Washington Consortium, 1997-1998. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Germanna (File Sent to Department of Historic Resources Archives), 1994-1998. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Gilmore Civil War Trust, 1999. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Goochland County Entry Corridor and Village, 2003-2004. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Goochland County Rural Preservation Zoning District Ordinance, 2004. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Goochland County Survey, 2002-2004. (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Gordon House (File Sent to Department of Historic Resources Archives), 1990-1991. (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Goshen Truss Bridge: Rockbridge County, Va., 2002. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Government Island, 2000. (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Government Island Committee, 1999. (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Government Performance Results Act (GPRA), 2004-2005. (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Governor's History Initiative, 1994-1995. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Governor Gilmore, 1998-2000. (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Governor's Mansion, 1999-2000. (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Governor - Misc.), 1994-1997. (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Governor's Natural Resource Partnership, 2005. (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Governor's Outdoor Resources Advisory Panel, 2003. (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Governor's Leadership Forum, 2006. (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Grace Episcopal Church: Yorktown, Va., 2002-2005. (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Grant Awards, 1999-2005. (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Grants Information, 1994-1998. (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Great American Main Street, 2001. (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Capitol Square: Va. Capitol Preservation Foundation SAT Grant Request, 2003-2005. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Capitol Square: Renovations, Media, 2003-2005. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Capitol Square: Va. Capitol Preservation Foundation, 2003-2005. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Capitol Square: PPEA, Fundraising, The Public, Visitors Center, History, 2003-2005. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Capitol Square: Bill Signing, Legislative Wives, 2003-2005. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Capitol Square: Reception, 2003-2005. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Capitol Square: 8th and 9th Street Buildings Feasibility Study, 2005. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Capitol Square: ACORN letter and Response, 8th and 9th Street Building Meeting, 2005. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Certified Local Governments, 1995-2004. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - CFS - Delegates/Assembly, 1998. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Charette, Va. State Capitol Research Book, 2006. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Chesapeake Bay Agreement, 2000-2002. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Capitol Square: Va. Capitol Preservation Foundation SAT grant request, 2003-2005. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Digging in Virginia: Fort Powhatan, 2004. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Director's Report File, 2001-2006. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Director's Speeches, 1996-1998. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Disney File (1), 1994. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Disney File (2), 1994. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Dispute Resolution Act, 2002. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Diversity Preservation Issues, 2001. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Division Head Meetings, 1994. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Douthat State Park, 2006. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Department of Social Services (DSS), 2001-2003. (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Dunklin Monument, 2000. (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Environment Alliance for Seniot Involvement (EASI) (1), 2002. (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - EASI (2), 2004. (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Economic Benefits, 2001-2002. (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Economic Development/ Japanese Governors, 1994-1996. (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Eighth Street Office Building, 2002-2005. (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Emergency Reports, 1996. (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Emergency Response Wheel, 1998. (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Endangered Historical Sites, 2006. (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Environment Virginia/ Amy DeHart, 2008. (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Environment Virginia, 2005. (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Environmental Review, 2005. (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Executive Contracts, 2002. (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Parker, Poe, Adams and Bernstein, 1996. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Partners for Sacred Places, 2001. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Pebble Creek: Hanover County, Va., 2002-2004. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Piedmont Website, 2000. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Performance Budgeting, 1997. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Performance Measures, 1996-1998. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Performance 1995, 1995. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Permits - Cave Permits, 1995. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Petersburg - 250th Anniversary, 1998-2005. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Philadelphia, Pa., unknown. (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Pine Knot, 1996. (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Pinkerton, Rennie, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Planning and Budget, 1994-1999. (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Planning List, unknown. (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Plaque Suppliers, 1995. (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Plenary Staff Meetings, 1996-2005. (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Pocahontas Mine, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Policy and Procedure - Department of Historic Resources, 1996. (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Policy Issues, 1996. (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Portlock School, 1995. (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Portsmouth Regional Office and Newsletter, 1996-1998. (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Potomac Gauntlet - ABPP Funding for Maryland, 2005. (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Poulton Morecambe, 1996. (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Powhatan Scenic Byways, 2004. (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Preliminary Information Package - Masters, 1995-1997. (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Preservation of Underwater Quarry, 1997. (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Preservation Action, 2004-2005. (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Preservation Advocate News, 1996. (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Preservation Alliance of Virginia, 2002. (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Preservation Criteria - Local, 1987. (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Preservation Newsletters, 1995. (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Preservation Services, 1994-1995. (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Prestwould Plantation: Mecklenburg County, Va., 2003. (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Prince William County, William Grayson's Tomb and Belle Aire Plantation, 1997. (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Privatization, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Productivity Savings, 2000. (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Program Audit/ Planning, 1990-1993. (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Cultural Tourism Conference, 1996. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Cumberland State Forest Trip and E-Mails, 2004-2005. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia Campaign, 1997. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Czech Visitor Profiles, 1996. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Dabney, 1999-2001. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Dan River Project, 2001. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Danville, 1995-1999. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Deane Hall, 1995-1996. (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Delegate, 1998. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Department of Forestry, 1998. (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Department of Environmental Quality (DEQ) Organizational Structure, 1998-2003. (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Department of Historic Resources (DHR) Code Section - Va. Landmark Register Certificates, 1996-1997. (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Department of Historic Resources History Initiative, 1994. (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Department of Historic Resources 40th Anniversary: Monticello, 2006. (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Digitization, 1997. (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Department of Historic Resources/ Virginia Historical Society Partnership, 1996. (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Department of Historic Resources Move and History Process, 1996-1998. (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Department of Historic Resources Programs, 1996-1998. (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - 1966-2007; Bulk 1990-1999 (Accession 50423)., 17 cu. ft. (17 boxes)
    - Henricus College, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Department of Historic Resources Priorities for 1997, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Main Street Managers Meeting, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Marketing Symposium, 1996 Sept. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Natural Bridge Dedication Ceremony, 1997 May 7. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - University of Virginia Newsletter, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Year End Tracking, 1995-1996. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Senate Committee Meeting, 1994 October 9-11. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Southern Governors' Association, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - State Comprehensive Plan, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Jamestown 2007, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Howard MacCord, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - New Jersey, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Op-ed by Alex Wise, 1998. (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Performance Measures, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Plenary Staff Meetings, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Transition Submission, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Governor's School - Richmond, 1997. (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Financial Incentive Guide - Putting Virginia's Historic Resources to Work, 1997-1998. (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Virginia Department of Economic Development, 1992. (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Virginia Association of Counties, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Transparencies, 1994-1995. (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - National Register of Historic Places, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Virginia Historical Preservation Foundations, 1996-1997. (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous - Planning List, 1995-2000. (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Historical Society, 1995-1996. (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Legislative Proposal, 1997-1998. (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Georgia Department of Natural Resources, 1994-1998. (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Virginia Department of Transportation, 1996-1999. (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Virginia Code Commission, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - National Association of State Archaeologists, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - National Park Service, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Department of Historic Resources - Legislative Proposal, 1995. (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Roy Wheeler Reality Co., 1996. (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Bermuda Hundred, 1995. (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Tettegouche Camp, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Roanoke Regional Preservation Office, 1994-1999. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Robins Foundation, 2003. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Rockbridge County, 2004-2005. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Route 58, 1994. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Route 3, 1998. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Roxbury Plantation (Spotsylvania County), 2001. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Rural Crescent Heritage Sites (Preserve America), 2006. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Salem, City of, 1996. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Santa Fe, 1997. (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Save America's Treasures Program, 1999-2005. (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Save Our History/The History Channel, 2004. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Savings Bonds, 1998. (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Scenic Virginia, 2003-2006. (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Schooner, Virginia, 2004. (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Schulerf, Delegate, 1997. (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Sea Hunt, 2001. (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - S.E. SHPO Conference, 1999. (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Secretary Correspondence re: Department of Historic Resources, 1995-1996. (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Secretary of Administration, 1994. (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1994. (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources, 1994. (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources, 1995. (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources, 1996. (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Secretary of Natural Resources, 1997. (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Secretary Retreat, 1998. (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Section 106 Revised Regulations, 1999. (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Section 106, 2004. (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Section 106, 2000-2004. (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Selden Arcade (Norfolk), 2002. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Senate, U.S., 1994-1996. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Senate bill 514, 1992. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Senate Joint Resolution 162, 1989-1991. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Senator - Congressmen, 2006. (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Senate, 1994-1995. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Senior Preservation Planner - UVA Search Committee, 2004. (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Shenandoah Community, 1995. (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Shenandoah Courthouse File, 2007. (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Skymeadows State Park, 2006. (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Slavery Museum Grant, 1997. (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Small Business Service Providers, 2002. (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Smithsonian Folk Life Festival, 2004. (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Society of Architectural Building of Virginia, 1995. (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Solving Histories Mysteries, 1999. (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Sons of the American Revolution, Virginia Society of, 2001-2004. (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Southeast Conference Evaluation Form, 1999. (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Southeastern SHPO COnference, 1999. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Save Outdoor Sculpture, 1999. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - South Market Street (18020) Staunton, Virginia, 2003. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Southeast Crescent Authority, 2003. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Southeastern Albemarle Rural Historic District, 2004. (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Southeastern Environmental Law Center (SELC), 2005. (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Spain, 1998. (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Spotsylvania County, 2004. (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - State Appropriations, 1998-1999. (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - State Comprehensive Plan, 1996. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - State Environmental Agency Conference, 2002. (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - SERP Program, 1996. (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - State Grants, 1996-2005. (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - State Hazard Mitigation Planning Committee, 2004. (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - State Parks Referendum, 2002. (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - State Review Board, 1983-1997. (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - State Review Board Members, 1966-1996. (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - State-Owned Stewardship, 2004. (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - State-Owned Building Survey (1 of 2), 1988-1991. (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - State-Owned Building Survey (2 of 2), 1988-1991. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Statuary - Virginia, 2004. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Statewide Preservation Plan, 1993-1994. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Stewardship Report 2007, 1996/2007. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Strike Force, 1994. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Structure of Virginia's Natural Resources Secretariat, 1997. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Student Conservation Association, 2002. (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Suburban Sprawl, 1999-2002. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Surry County Courthouse, 2002. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Survey and Planning, 2000-2004. (Box 32, Folder 10)